https://www.mtbuller.com.au/Winter/terms-and-conditions

Lift Passes
What is a B-TAG?
Lift Passes
What is a B-TAG?
Terms and Conditions
AgreementMtbuller.com.au (site) is owned and operated by Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board ABN 44 867 982 534 of Mt Buller, Victoria, Australia and Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd ABN 25 153 985 829 of Level 35, Rialto North Tower, 525 Collins Street VIC 3000. These terms and conditions together with any additional terms, disclaimers and notices contained on this site form the terms and conditions of access to and use of this site. By using this site you confirm that you agree with these terms and conditions and any changes thereto and acknowledge to be bound by them. If you do not agree with these terms and conditions, you should immediately stop using this site.
DisclaimerThe material on this site is provided in good faith on ‘as is' basis. Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board, Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd, its related body corporate and their directors, employees or agents do not make any representation or warranty that the material available on this site is true, accurate, complete or free from errors or that your access to this site will be uninterrupted. Your use of this site and the material is entirely at your own risk. The material on this site without limitation provide general information only. Such material is not intended as advice and must not be relied upon as such.
IndemnityYou indemnify and agree to continue to indemnify Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board, Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd its related body corporate and officers against any claim, demand, costs, loss or damages, in connection with or arising out of any breach of these terms and conditions or any other terms of this site or third party proprietary rights by you, your use of this site or your conduct on this site.
Links to Third Party WebsitesThis site provides hyperlinks to third party websites solely as a convenience to you. If you use any of these links, you will leave this site. Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board and Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd has not reviewed these third party websites, does not control these websites and is not responsible for the contents on these websites. Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board, Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd and this site do not endorse any material, goods or services available on the third party websites. If you visit any of these websites or purchase any goods or services from them, you do so at your own risk.
AdvertisementsThis site may from time to time display third party advertisements. Such advertisements may or may not contain hyperlinks to third party websites. You acknowledge that display of such advertisement does not in any way imply that Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board, Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd or this site endorse or recommend the goods or services of such advertisers or their websites. If you purchase any goods or services from them or visit any of their websites, you do so at your own risk.
Intellectual PropertyThe material available on this site is copyright protected. Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board and Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd authorises you to view and download such material for your personal non-commercial use provided you retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the original material. Such material may not otherwise be used, copied, reproduced, published, distributed, transmitted, disseminated, altered or stored in any form or by any means without the prior written approval of Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board and Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd. Mtbuller.com.au and other trademarks and logos displayed on this site from time to time are the trademarks of Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board, Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd, its related body corporate and/or third parties. Display of these trademarks on this site does not grant and should not be construed as granting, any right or licence to use the trademarks.
Limitation of LiabilityMt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board and Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd makes no warranties or representations to you either express or implied and expressly excludes to the full extent permitted by the applicable law, all liabilities (including without limitation, all consequential damages, if any) relating to accuracy, quality, standard, safety, fitness or suitability for any purpose of any material, goods or services supplied or offered by Mt Buller and Mt StirlingAlpine Resort Management Board on this site. To the extent permitted by the applicable law, Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board's liability for breach of any implied warranty or condition that can not be excluded lawfully is limited to:
in the case of goods supplied by Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board and Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd:
the repair of the goods;
the replacement or resupply of the goods;
payment of the costs of having the goods repaired; or
payment of the costs of having the goods replaced;
in the case of services supplied by Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board and Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd:
resupply of the services;
payment of the costs of resupply of services.
Privacy PolicyYou agree and authorise Mt Buller and Mt Stirling Alpine Resort Management Board, Buller Ski Lifts Pty Ltd and its agents to do each of the following:
collect your personal information provided by you on this site; and
use the personal information for administering and operating this site and for marketing purposes such as planning, researching, promoting and/or marketing any goods and/or services of mtbuller.com.au and/or a third party by email, mail or telephone; and
disclose and/or transfer the personal information to related bodies corporate, officers, employees and agents of mtbuller.com.au.
Mt Buller is party to the Mountain Collective Program and Ikon (Alterra Mountain Company) cross resorts pass products agreements.  If you visit us using one of these passes we will scan or otherwise record your attendance at our resort location using RFID technology (radio frequency identification), handheld scanners, or another method which allows us to record your usage activity. We will share this information with the Mountain Collective Program and the Alterra Mountain Company in order for them to administer their cross resorts pass products.
Why do we use cookies?
They help us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website, and also allow us to improve our site. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that you have agreed we may store on your browser or your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.
What type of cookies do we use?
Strictly necessary cookiesThese are cookies are required for the operation of our website. They include, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website.
Analytical/performance cookiesThey allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works.
Targeting cookiesThese cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.
Third-party cookies
Our websites may set several types of third-party cookies; however, we do not control the operation of them.
The third-party cookies that may be set include:
Google Analytics – www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
Facebook – https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/.
You can block cookies by changing the settings on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.
You can access, update or correct or request to delete any personal information relating to you held in mtbuller.com.au database by contacting the administrator at info@mtbuller.com.au.
In the event of any inconsistency between these Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy, the Privacy Policy shall prevail.
NoticesAll notices to a party shall be sent by email.
Applicable LawThese Terms and Conditions and all other matters arising from or related to your use or access to this site are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the state of Victoria, Australia. You expressly submit to the jurisdiction of the courts in the state of Victoria, Australia.
Please read the Privacy Policy for the purchase of B-TAGs and other products from Buller Ski Lifts Pty here.
SEE US IN SUMMER
Our Sponsors:
Terms and Conditions
Sister Resorts
buy online
accommodation
searchaccommodation
Arrive
Depart
Adults
search
Did you know that your Internet Browser is out of date?
Your browser is out of date (Internet Explorer version 8 or under), and may not be compatible with our website. A list of the most popular web browsers can be found below.Just click on the icons to get to the download page
Google Chrome
Mozilla Firefox
Safari
Internet Explorer
